Okay.
Our fish has been in the oven for about 20 minutes, so now it's time to take it out.
You can see the garlic is still in there, and here's our fish packet.
Yum.
The garlic still needs to cook.
Here we go.
Now, we're just going to let this sit here and do what I like to call residual cooking.
Actually, all meats do that when you take them out of the heat, the heat that's in there continues to cook the meat.
And that's what's going to keep it really moist and incredibly delicious texture, soft texture.
So meanwhile, let's just quickly do our broccoli.
This is -- we're just going take our knife and the broccoli, and just cut the ends off of our florets like so.
Just enough for two people is what we need to do.
And if you have more than two people, you're welcome to save these stems and eat them too, if you'd like.
I happen to prefer just the broccoli florets.
And to this, we're going to go over to the sink so we can put an inch of water.
We just need a little bit of water in here at the bottom -- just a little bit of water.
And I'm going to put the broccoli florets in here like so.
I'm going to cover them, and I'm going to put them on the stove -- here we go -- and I'm going to boil them with high heat.
So just that little bit of water is really going to be more like steaming, so it's not going to be overcooked so it's going to be a bright green.
And I'm going to check them every once in a while, but it takes about 10 minutes to cook.
So keep clicking, we're getting close to putting it all together.